Eduardo Molina

11401 Dr M.L.K Jr St N Apt 2006 St. Petersburg, FL 33716

M +1 (786) 567-2231

edrdmolina11@gmail.com

www.edmolina.com

Profile

After working in Aviation Maintenance for over 6 years I decided to take on a new challenge. With an existing interest in creativity and engineering, I realized I can contribute to a field that delivers solutions that grow businesses, automate complex tasks and provides data to the masses. Now, as a highly motivated Web Developer eager to learn and grow within the Software Development field. I am ready to join a team and make a positive impact.

Experience

QC Inspector, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida – 2018-2020

Responsible for performing tear-down inspections, in process inspections and final inspections on aerostructures to ensure conformity with manufacturer specifications. I was assigned to the travel team as a team leader. As the team leader, I directed the team to perform repairs and was responsible for communication with the customer and the engineering team, inspecting for discrepancies and coordinating the repair process to ensure conformity with manufacturer specifications.

Radome Testing Unit Operator, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida - 2016-2018

Performed radio transmissivity inspections on Nose Radomes to ensure repairs performed allow for radio transmissions as required by manufacturer specifications. Required troubleshooting in order to assess any discrepancies found during testing. Applied periodic maintenance to test unit. While in this position I was also tasked with coordinating with shop managers and repair technicians to schedule cure oven times.

Structures Repair Technician, Heico Aerostructures; Miami, Florida - 2014-2016

Tasked with performing minor and major repairs on sheet metal and composite structures while keeping track of all materials and processes. All repairs performed required following instructions supplied by the manufacturer or an on-site engineering team.

Education

The Modern React Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
The Bootstrap 4 Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
The Web Developer Bootcamp - Colt Steele, 2021
CS50x - David J. Malan, 2021
George T. Baker - Aircraft Technician, 2017

Skills

Javascript, React JS, Node JS, Express JS, EJS, SQL, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap 4 & 5, SCSS.